{
  "type": "writing",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "Wùlǐ" ,
      "answer": "物理"
    },
    {
      "question": "Huàxué",
      "answer": "化学"
    },
    {
      "question": "Shùxué" ,
      "answer": "数学"
    },
    {
      "question": "Yīnyuè",
      "answer": "音乐"
    },
    {
      "question": "Lìshǐ",
      "answer": "历史"
    },
    {
      "question": "Zhéxué",
      "answer": "哲学"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jīngjì",
      "answer": "经济"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jiàoyù",
      "answer": "教育"
    },
    {
      "question": "Xuǎnxiū",
      "answer": "选修"
    },
    {
      "question": "Wénhuà",
      "answer": "文化"
    }
  ]
}
